[{"answer": "Nowadays you have to... soften it", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Because, I don't want it softened", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You told your parents about me, then", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I think you're crackers, but go on.  I'm riveted", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": ".\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Milk", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hang up the phone", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Do it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "If you don't want money, what do you want", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hear about what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What about this weekend", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Grounded?  What for", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Can you blow that the other way", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No, I do", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Maybe you don't like me", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Maybe you don't like girls", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Just to be safe", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, relax, old man.  Sit down and open it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Are you out of your fucking mind?  I'm going to get three or four flunk cards.  I failed an economics test today, so there's another one", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I could have done better myself", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, I suppose I won't", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "And so it comes to an end.  Here", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "A good break for you, my friend", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, it seems my friend didn't do to well in A.P. biology", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Christ, I forgot.  my friend, my aunt my friend, Dad's sister, died on Wednesday.  Mom and Dad have to drive up to that place to settle her estate. We can't ask Dad to drive six hours each way for graduation", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "That's why.  You understand, don't you, my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend.  He had a heart attack", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, he's awake.  I'm really scared.  The address is 9", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Did you need something", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Mr. my friend has been moved.  I'm going to give you something.  It will help you sleep", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We have all we need here, my friend", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "My name is my friend, that place.  This is Detective my friend from the that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That's right.  I was.  That's what I was doing there.  It was in German but he insisted I try to read it anyway.  Once or twice he got pissy about the pronunciation but I asked him what did he want from me.  I don't speak German.  Mr. my friend... Dussander... got really excited at one point. He yelled out,", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "That's right", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Wait, I saw a letter.  It was in German.  I didn't think anything of it at the time. But, yeah, it was on Airmail stationery", "docId": "Apt-Pupil.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It isn't", "qsentId": 36}]